Guide to the Joy Golden Papers, 1956-2012 RL.00461
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1979-2005 and undated, 13 boxes
  - Compilations
    - Joy Radio Reel 19A: 19 spots. 1992-1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 19:00 (Box AV13)
    - Joy Radio Reel 19B: 17 spots. 1992-1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 17:00 (Box AV13)
    - Joy Radio Reel 20: 14 spots. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 14:00 (Box AV13)
    - Joy Radio Reel 21: 11 spots. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 11:00 (Box AV13)
    - Joy Radio Reel 22: 14 spots. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 14:00 (Box AV13)
    - Joy Radio Reel 23: 13 spots. 1994-1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 13:00 (Box AV13)
    - Joy Radio Reel 24: 12 spots. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 12:00 (Box AV13)
    - Joy Radio Reel 24B: 10 spots. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV13)
    - Joy Radio Reel 25: 14 spots. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 14:00 (Box AV13)
    - 9 Promos. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 9:00 (Box AV13)
    - 10 Spots Used in LA. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV13)
    - 11 Little Funnies. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 11:00 (Box AV13)
    - 13 Selected Spots. 1986. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 13:00 (Box AV13)
    - 14 Funnies. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 14:00 (Box AV13)
    - 15 Funnies. 1999. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 15:00 (Box AV13)
    - A Casting Extravaganza. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - A Few Food-Related Spots. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - A Little Comedy, A Little Jewish. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - A Little Wit. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - Announcerville. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 60:00 (Box AV13)
    - Banks/Finance: 8 spots. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 8:00 (Box AV13)
    - Best of Fall: 13 spots. 1986. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 13:00 (Box AV13)
    - Broadcast Radio: 8 spots. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 8:00 (Box AV13)
    - Cool Hip Groovy Youth-Oriented: 6 spots. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 6:00 (Box AV13)
    - Direct Reponse/Blue Star Foods: 5 spots. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV13)
    - Everywhere but NYC: 8 spots. 1998. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 8:00 (Box AV13)
    - Financial Services/Banks: 4 spots. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV13)
    - Food/Beverage: 10 spots. 1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV13)
    - Golden cont'd: 12 spots. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 12:00, 3 tapes (Box AV13)
    - Golden Oldies and Newies. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 2 tapes (Box AV13)
    - In the Public Interest (PSAs): 7 spots. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 7:00 (Box AV13)
    - Jewish Reel: 25 spots. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 25:00, 2 tapes (Box AV13)
    - Jingle Reel: 5 spots. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV13)
    - Joy Golden Radio. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - Max Factor; Amtrak; Splendor Shampoo; Stetson. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 6:00 (Box AV13)
    - Monster Reel: 27 spots. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 27:00 (Box AV13)
    - Naughty Spots: 10 spots. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV13)
    - Non-New York Spots: 8 spots. 1998. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 8:00 (Box AV13)
    - Party Music. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - Recent Classics: 5 spots. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV13)
    - Short Promos Reel: 11 spots. 1997. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 11:00 (Box AV13)
    - Some Retail Spots: 6 spots. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 6:00 (Box AV13)
    - Some Serious Stuff. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - Specialty Spots: 13 spots (bank and finance). Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 13:00 (Box AV13)
    - Teenage Spots: 5 spots. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV13)
    - Updated WASP Reel: 9 spots. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 9:00 (Box AV13)
    - Witty Reel: 10 spots. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV13)
    - Youth and Retail Spots: 7 spots. 1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 7:00 (Box AV13)
  - Interviews, Speeches, Appearances
    - A Few Speech Elements (7 spots). 1998. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 7:00 (Box AV13)
    - Ad Women of New York speech. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - ANA speech reel. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - ANA speech: 15 funnies. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 15:00 (Box AV13)
    - ATT speech: 10 spots. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV13)
    - Bob Greene's answer to Joy Houston Ad Federation speech. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - Barry Gray interview. 1985. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 2 tapes (Box AV13)
    - Best of Life. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - Carillon Travelena Sales Meeting. 1985. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 17:30 (Box AV13)
    - Cassette for Learning Annex. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - Change of Life. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 6 tapes (Box AV13)
    - Comedy Night. 1996-1998. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 3 tapes (Box AV13)
    - Dallas interview. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - Doj Sokoe's show. 1986. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - Feature on Joy Golden for A.P. Radio's Portfolio show. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - Great American Songwriters vol. 2: Johnny Mercer (Rhino records). 1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 45:00 (Box AV13)
    - Here Comes My Third Husband Now. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 60:00 (Box AV13)
    - Interview reel: 7 spots. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 7:00 (Box AV13)
    - Interview with Judge Howard Goldfluss. 1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - Joe's first narration. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - Joy's dialogue (Joe). Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - Joy's gig at Caroline's. 1996. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - Ken Behren's show (WJBC Bloomington Ill). Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - King of the One Liners. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - KMBR interview. 1985. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - Late in My Life. 1984. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 7 tapes (Box AV13)
    - Leon. 1984. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - London speech. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 13:00, 2 tapes (Box AV13)
    - London workshop. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 2 tapes (Box AV13)
    - Loner and Commitment. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - Making a Good Radio Commercial. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 2 tapes (Box AV13)
    - Nora. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - NPR interview. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 2 tapes (Box AV13)
    - NPR; William B. Williams; Barry Gray interview compilation. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - Pitty's class speech. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - Reunion. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - Séance. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - Sell It With Music. 1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - Television Academy, 9 spots. 1986. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 9:00 (Box AV13)
    - Toronto. 1998. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - U-Turn. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - Video Dating. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - WABC interview. 1986. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - WNEW interview, William B. Williams. 1985. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 3 tapes (Box AV13)
    - White Bowling Ball. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV13)
    - YWCA speech: 9 spots. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 9:00 (Box AV13)